http://www.calvaryag.com.sg/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
This is a Calvary Assembly of God Church website.
We respect the privacy of individuals and are committed to protecting the personal data of individuals which we collect in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (“PDPA”).
By providing your personal information to us, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this privacy statement.
If you are only browsing this website or using the search function, we do not capture data that allows us to identify you individually. This website automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page(s) requested. Please note that this website may contain links to other websites not maintained by us. Such third party websites are subject to their own data protection and privacy practices and you are encouraged to examine the privacy policies of those websites.
We may use the personal information that you provide for the purposes for which the personal data was collected, including:-
(a) To respond to your queries;
(b) To provide you with information on our ministries and programmes;
(c) To contact you for any activities relating to our Church, ministries and programmes;
(d) To administer your Church-related applications, such as for Water Baptism and Church Membership and our Life groups;
(e) For our internal records and administrative purposes.
We may disclose your personal information to third parties whom we have engaged to maintain this website or to protect the security or integrity of this website and our databases. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that such third parties do not use your personal information for a purpose other than the purposes for which the personal information were originally given.
We may disclose your information in special circumstances, such as where the disclosure is necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of the Church, our members, our staff, or any other relevant person, or where otherwise required by law.
We undertake to keep strictly secret and confidential the personal information provided by you save and except where disclosure may be required to be made pursuant to any applicable laws and regulations or is permitted under this privacy statement.
We reserve the right to vary, modify or amend any terms of this privacy statement from time to time. Any variation, modification or amendment of any terms of this privacy statement shall apply with immediate effect.
This Policy shall be interpreted, construed and governed by the laws of Singapore.
Should you have any enquiries, feedback or comments relating to your personal information collected by us, you may contact our office at admin@calvaryag.com.sg
Last Updated on 21 February 2016
CLOSE
